fantasyfootball.com 2007-12-10

# fantasyfootball.com: Privacy Policy

**Fantasy Planet Privacy Policy**

Fantasy Planet considers the maintenance of user privacy to be extremely important. Following is a description of the manner in which Fantasy Planet manages user information ("Privacy Policy" or "Policy"). 

**Scope**

  * The Policy covers describes the manner in which Fantasy Planet treats personal information that it collects and/or receives, including information related to a user’s historical use of Fantasy Planet and Fantasy Planet affiliate services. A user’s personal information is information that is personally identifiable, such as the user’s name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 
  * The Fantasy Planet Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Fantasy Planet does not own or control, or to people or entities that Fantasy Planet does not employ or manage. In addition, certain Fantasy Planet affiliates and promotional partners may have their own privacy policy(ies), which may be viewed separately at the affiliates’ or partners'website(s), as applicable. 

Collection and Use of User Information 

**General**

  * Fantasy Planet collects personal information when you register with Fantasy Planet.com, or with an affiliate fantasy sports or content partner of Fantasy Planet.com. Fantasy Planet may record information when you visit Fantasy Planet.com pages or the pages of Fantasy Planet affiliates. Fantasy Planet may combine information it collects with information it obtains from business partners or other companies. 
  * When you register, Fantasy Planet asks for information such as your name, email address, age, gender, zip code, occupation, and referral information. Once you register with Fantasy Planet and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 
  * As part of the registration process, you are given an option to receive periodic email promotions from Fantasy Planet partners. You may change your preferred setting in this regard at any time by visiting your "My Profile" link or emailing [](http://webmaster@fantasyplanet.com/)[](mailto:webmaster@fantasyplanet.com)[](mailto:webmaster@fantasyplanet.com)[webmaster@fantasyplanet.com](mailto:webmaster@fantasyplanet.com)[](mailto:webmaster@fantasyplanet.com). 
  * Fantasy Planet collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners. Fantasy Planet automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Fantasy Planet and/or affiliate cookie information, and the page(s) you request. 
  * Fantasy Planet uses the information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. If you opt to receive periodic email promotions from Fantasy Planet partners, Fantasy Planet may also use your information to send you the promotions, or may make your information available to partners to send the promotions. Should you change your mind, and wish to stop receiving promotional offers from Fantasy Planet or its partners, you can follow the “Unsubscribe” link in any email that you receive, or you can send an email to [](mailto:support@fantasyplanet.com)[](mailto:support@fantasyplanet.com)[support@fantasyplanet.com](mailto:support@fantasyplanet.com) with the word “Unsubscribe” in the subject line. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * Fantasy Planet does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies, except to provide promotional materials for products or services when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 
    * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Fantasy Planet under agreements restricting the use of user information in substantially the same manner as set forth in this Policy. These companies may use your personal information to help Fantasy Planet communicate with you about offers from Fantasy Planet and our marketing partners. 
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; 
    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Fantasy Planet’ terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 
    * We transfer information about you if Fantasy Planet is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Fantasy Planet will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 
  * Fantasy Planet displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria. 
    * Fantasy Planet does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. 
  * Fantasy Planet does not share your credit card information or other payment information with outside parties, except as may be necessary to process payments that you authorize, or as may be required by order of law. 

**Cookies**

  * Fantasy Planet may set and access Fantasy Planet cookies on your computer. 
  * Fantasy Planet may permit advertisers on some of its pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this Policy. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Fantasy Planet’ cookies. 

Your Ability to Edit Your Account Information and Preferences 

**General**

  * You can edit your Fantasy Planet user profile, including your personal information and marketing preferences, at any time. 
  * New categories of marketing communications may be added to the opt-in section of your Profile page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive. 
  * Fantasy Planet reserves the right to send you certain communications relating to the Fantasy Planet service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and game newsletters, that are considered part of your Fantasy Planet account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. 
  * You can unsubscribe from your account by replying to any Fantasy Planet email with the word “Unsubscribe” in the reply subject line. 

**Confidentiality and Security**

  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 
  * Fantasy Planet employs physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

  * Fantasy Planet may update this Policy at any time. Fantasy Planet will notify you about significant changes in the way it treats personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Fantasy Planet account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

**Questions and Support**

  * If you have questions about this Policy, including any relationship between Fantasy Planet and its affiliates and/or partners, please send an email to [](mailto:support@Fantasy)[support@Fantasy](mailto:support@Fantasy) Planet.com, or send your question to: 

Fantasy Planet, L.P.  
Customer Support  
4245 Kemp Suite 818  
Wichita Falls, TX 76308  
(866) 475-9002
